<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tags on Abhinav&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://abhi9.in/blog/tags/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tags on Abhinav&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 03:31:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://abhi9.in/blog/tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Huawei E5573Cs-609</title>
      <link>https://abhi9.in/blog/2020/07/huawei-e5573cs-609/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 03:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abhi9.in/blog/2020/07/huawei-e5573cs-609/</guid>
      <description>Huawei E5573Cs-609 Setup Install
 Huawei drivers.zip dc-unlocker2client_1.00.1431.zip  Writing IMEI: In DC unlocker, after detecting the device, write following command
AT^CIMEI=&amp;quot;Replace with your IMEI number&amp;quot;  Writing Serial no: AT^SN=&amp;quot;16digit serial number&amp;quot;  To use without battery: AT^NVWREX=50364,0,4,01 00 00 00   Note: It may erase IMEI and serial number. So it needs to be rewrite.
 To undo this:
AT^NVWREX=50364,0,4,00 00 00 00  Ref:
 https://forum.hovatek.com/thread-32528.html  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Create Angular Library</title>
      <link>https://abhi9.in/blog/2020/04/how-to-create-angular-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 15:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abhi9.in/blog/2020/04/how-to-create-angular-library/</guid>
      <description>Create a workspace ng new my-workspace --create-application=false  This will initialized a project without creating any app module and all.
Create a library The following command will create a library.
ng g library @scope/my-library  The library source will be in
/my-workspace |-- projects |-- scope |--my-library |-- src |-- lib  You can skip the scope part if you don&amp;rsquo;t want and name your library like my-library
Build your library Under /my-workspace directory run</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog = Joplin &#43; Hugo &#43; Github</title>
      <link>https://abhi9.in/blog/2020/04/blog-joplin-hugo-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 04:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abhi9.in/blog/2020/04/blog-joplin-hugo-github/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been quite a while since I was thinking about writing a blog. The only thing that kept me away from writing is set of tools which are easy, quick and more imporantly can fuse with my day-to-day note taking process.
Swith to Joplin I was using Boostnote as note taking app but it lacks mobile app, web-clipper and sychronization features; moreover it became very buggy lately. Then I switched to Jopline and it has all the feature as note taking app I was looking for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVM on Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://abhi9.in/blog/2020/02/nvm-on-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 04:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abhi9.in/blog/2020/02/nvm-on-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>It very simple to run nodejs on Windows 10.
 Get NVM-Windows from https://github.com/coreybutler/nvm-windows Open powershell and install node  nvm install 10 Close Powershell and open it agin. Run this to activate node version.  nvm use 10   Close Powershell.    Run Node App as Service on Windows  Download latest version from https://nssm.cc/download Extract the zip file To install a new service, open the Powershell  Run: cd /path/to/extracted/nssm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSSQL RDS Backup to S3</title>
      <link>https://abhi9.in/blog/2020/02/mssql-rds-backup-to-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 14:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abhi9.in/blog/2020/02/mssql-rds-backup-to-s3/</guid>
      <description>Create an Option groups with SQLSERVER_BACKUP_RESTORE option   Assign the group to RDS instance  Troubleshooting  The transaction log for database is full due to &amp;lsquo;ACTIVE_BACKUP_OR_RESTORE&amp;rsquo;.  Switch recovery mode to simple before triggering the backup
alter database TestimonialTree set recovery simple  After successful backup, switch back recovery to full
alter database TestimonialTree set recovery full  Ref: Perform Native Backups of SQL Server DB Instances</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
